she is from legal and she is potentially
a very expensive sexual harassment
lawsuit oddly more like that yes and
I've got three excellent potential
candidates better lined up and ready
meet you I don't have time to meet I
need someone now I feel like it's her no
it's not we have a box before I have yes
I like tae bo booty boot camp crunchy
something like that how do I spell your
name Natalie are you what are you gonna
google her hmm
I thought I was going her oh wow very
very impressive individual she's French
Italian Russian Latin who speaks Latin
no one speaks Latin there was dead
language you can read Latin or you can
write Latin but I'm yeah Kashima
[Music]